A Royal Christmas is a tv movie, romance, family film directed by Alex Zamm.
A young working girl with a blue-collar background is surprised when her new fiancé
announces he is actually a prince of a small sovereign country in Europe.
After the couple quickly takes off to spend the holidays at his family’s sprawling, royal castle, she must work hard to win
over her disapproving and unaccepting future mother-in-law—the Queen—and find out if love truly can conquer all.
Emily Taylor, played by Lacey Chabert.
Leo James / Prince Leopold, played by Stephen Hagan.
Queen Isadora, played by Jane Seymour.
Duchess Natasha, played by Katherine Flynn.
Baron Kent, played by Ionut Grama.
Bud Taylor, played by Mitchell Mullen.
A Royal Christmas is a 2014 American holiday romance television film directed by
Alex Zamm and starring Lacey Chabert, Stephen Hagan, and Jane Seymour.
Written by Janeen Damian, Michael Damian, Neal H.
Dobrofsky, and Tippi Dobrofsky, the film is about a young American seamstress from Philadelphia
whose boyfriend reveals himself to be a royal prince and heir to the throne of Aldovia.
He brings her to his country intending to marry her,
to the consternation of the Queen.
A Royal Christmas is an original Hallmark Channel movie and first
aired on the Hallmark Channel on November 21, 2014.
The tone is emotional.